in this video we will pay using the
manual life mobile app also
we will check out the different methods
to
advise our channel and Do
you still want online tutorial videos
like this please click the subscribe
button I have installed the manual life
app You can download it from the Play
Store or App Store and currently
I am logged in when you first
load
basically your email address and
password and then OTP will either be
sent to your email address or phone
number After that right away here on the
homepage you will see the policy that
you have with them there is also a portfolio
here payment option and your profile
where you can change
your password and username let's go back
here to payment because that is
our purpose in this video I will make a
payment this is my policy here is also the
amount and when is the J Dat
and just to add to this term insurance
so I will pay it before I go on duty
I just tap that here are the details
recent payment posting may take 2 to 3
days before it reflects as paid there on the
manual life side and like I said
Earlier we explored the different
methods of paying tap Ong here Let
's just continue B Let's exit
their app for payment You can
shop here below you can use the
manual life online which is what
we are already doing basically in the app
we will produce and we also showed a
separate video about it if In
GCash there is of course there is also in maya it's
almost the same method
you just choose the BS and then just look for
the manual life there in the list of billers
and provide your policy number you can also
via shopee
also in Lazada they have a wallet there
and via online banking you can use in
chinabank BDO BPI Metrobank ubp and
banknet now let's go back here to the app
where this is what I will use to
pay so my saap Ong pay
premium amount to pay is the total
and for payment methods there is only one
option available currently which is
the PESO pay and from here you can
provide our credit or debit card
details this is the 16 digit card
number they accept visa card and
Master card please choose the
relationship of card holder since  I
own a debit card that I will pay with
here I will put my own But you can also
use someone else's debit card here is
the list let's go back self
I chose I agree to the payment terms and
conditions continue to payment
let's go now the maya app is open
I went to cards because
my virtual card in maya is what I will use and has a
visa logo so obviously It's a visa card let's go
back here I tap the visa I
need to provide all the information
that is seen or required here so
my goodness I have completed all
the information the card number expiry
date also your card verification number
or cvv and email address By the way here
in Maya when you scan the virtual card
The information that is needed is
just tap on show card details and
you will see the 16 digit card
number the expiry date or valid through
date and our cvv my SOP is just
Ong
submit and review everything you see here
the card number expiry date
your name and email address also when
you verify just tap Ong
[Music]
okay and  I will send an OTP to the phone
number linked to
maya which is what I received in the
text and just put the
OTP here and tap submit By the way when
you receive an OTP, don't
give it to someone else it means
there is a transaction happening that
you need to approve that's why you
need to put the OTP just to make
sure that you are really paying your
payment transaction is completed it is
better to take a screenshot as
proof of payment you can also
print it so you have a backup copy
so I just tap
continue and you successfully processed
your payment I also received a
text from maya confirming this
transaction go to the home page and there is no
confirmation here or anything
about the payment instead if
we have an inquiry for the confirmation
we can go back to the App or we can also
double check in the manual Life by
Reaching Out to their support or
customer service and very quickly
the fees have also been reduced here on
my balance when I checked the transaction
history here at the bottom there is a
reduction  2,776 so clearly
my payment is free using my virtual card
in maya and also I am also taking advantage of
their promo to
increase the interest rate I
currently have because I am at 5% per anum if
I pay it further I can get
the higher interest rate or what
my money can earn while it is
sitting here in maya bank or
maya sav So you can also check this
and also be a reason for
choosing the payment method for
your insurance and if
you are interested in opening a maya savings
account where it offers a
higher interest rate for other
traditional banks you can check
these videos below I hope it helps
and see you in the next videos
ba-bye